WOMAN:
Do you know if enough people have registered for the computer class?
I have to let Mr.
Terrance know whether the class is going to open or not.
MEN:
I checked the list earlier,
and there were many who had already registered.
I think it's safe to tell Mr.
Terrance that the class is going to be held.
In fact, ask him if he would be interested in opening an extra class?
Registration lasts until this Friday,
and I think there is a good chance that we could fill another class.
WOMAN:
I think he would be happy to hear that.
I will call him right away to see what he says.
MEN:
Thanks,
and could you also do me a favor and see how many people have
registered for the cooking class?